本作品之片源来自互联网，仅供学习、交流之用。请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。任何组织和个人不得用于任何商业用途，否则一切后果请自行承担！如果喜欢本片，请购买正版！
翠西  合唱团有大危机了
Trish, we have a Glee club emergency.
我们男高音兰尼  先是被狗追
Our tenor, Lenny, was chased by a dog,
然后从自行车上掉下来摔断了腿
fell off his bike, and broke his leg.
哦  太棒了
Oh, great!
这说明我们今天不用彩排了
That means we don't have to rehearse today.
天啊  狗还真是人类的好朋友
Man, dogs really are man's best friend.
有点同情心好不好
Have some sympathy.
就是啊  可怜的兰尼可能六个星期
Yeah, poor Lenny's probably gonna be on crutches
都离不开拐杖了
for six weeks.
我是说同情同情我
I mean sympathy for me.
没有男高音
Without a tenor, there's no way
下周比赛我们不可能赢的
we'll win next week's competition.
我们很可能只得
We might end up in
第二名
Second place.
第二名已经能保证我们
Second place still qualifies you
晋级区赛了啊
for regionals.
哦  但是第二名就是没有赢
Oh, but second place is not winning.
第二名就是说你是个失败者
Second place means you're a loser.
嘿  我总是排第二的
Hey, I come in second place all the time.
你们会说我是失败者吗
Would you guys call me a loser?
你真想让我回答这个问题吗
Do you really want me to answer that?
还是算了吧
Probably not.
我得想办法  我是队长
I have to fix this. I'm the captain.
出问题的时候  整个合唱团都要靠我
When there's a problem, the whole club looks to me
我得淡定  冷静  从容不迫
to be calm, cool, and collected.
要这么说他们还是靠别的吧
Maybe they should look somewhere else.
我知道是怎么回事
I see what's going on.
她正在受一种罕见疾病的困扰
She's afflicted with a rare condition
叫做“人声合唱完美主义强迫症”
called "A capella persperitis,"
也俗称为
better known as
“合唱团热病”
"Glee fever!"
我自己就受到了点感染
I kind of have a touch of it myself,
但是从来都没治好过
but I'll never get cured
因为我一直都没进过合唱团
since I didn't get picked to be in Glee club.
要不是为了骗点学分  我的位子就让给你了
I'd give you my spot if I didn't need the extra credits.
我原来想去木工课的
I tried wood shop,
但是用电锯的时候睡着
but apparently it's "Dangerous"
明显是属于“危险”的
to fall asleep while operating a buzz saw.
别跑题
Focus.
我们得在紧急情况下找个人替代兰尼
We need to find a last minute replacement for Lenny.
他必须要唱得好  学得快
He needs to be a strong singer who can learn fast.
上哪儿找这样的人啊
Where are you gonna find that?
她跋涉千山万水来与人相聚
She'll be coming around the Mountain when she comes.
德兹  嘘
Dez! Shh.
我们在想事呢
We're trying to think.
你们也得找个有魅力的人
You also need someone with charisma
会跳舞的
and good dance moves.
哪个我们认识的人是这样的啊
Who do we know?
天啊  我们怎么这么傻
Gosh, what's wrong with us?
我们已经知道谁最合适了啊
We already know the perfect person.
那当然
Of course.
他一直就在我们眼前
He's been right in front of us the whole time.
艾丽  这是我的荣幸
Ally, it would be my honor.
奥斯汀
Austin!
你应该加入合唱团
You should be in Glee club.
为什么不呢
Why not?
你们也找不到别人了
Since you can't find anyone else.
- 耶  - 就这么定了  太棒了
- Yeah. - All right, cool.
再见  德兹
Bye, Dez.
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录www.Deefun.com
观众意犹未尽之时
When the crowd wants more
我来点燃更多激情
I bring on the thunder
因为有你为我撑腰
'cause you've got my back
我不会临阵退缩的
and I'm not going under
■
翻译： CandyS
你是我的唯一  你是我的守护
you're my point, you're my guard
你是最完美的和声
you're the perfect chord
我看见咱俩一同出现在各大广告牌上
and I see our names together on every billboard
■
校订： 战忽局副局座
我们勇攀高峰  势在必得
we're headed for the top, we've got it on lock
我们让他们大声说“嘿”
we'll make 'em say "Hey!"
然后我们继续前进
and we'll keep rockin'
■
后期： 战忽局副局座  happy4041
前进的路上怎能没有你
oh, there's no way I could make it without ya
你不可或缺  你不可替代
do it without ya, be here without ya
快乐需要与你分享
it's no fun when you're doing it solo
在你身边总有惊喜  而且我还知道
with you it's like, "Whoa," Yeah, and I know
我为梦想而奋斗
I own this dream
因为有你伴我左右
'cause I got you with me
前进的路上怎能没有你
there's no way I could make it without ya
你不可或缺  你无可替代
do it without ya, be here without ya.
奥斯汀与艾丽  第三季第六集
Austin and Ally S03E06 Glee Clubs & Glory
队员们  都动作快点
Hustle up, b-sharps.
跟你们的新队友  流行歌手奥斯汀·穆恩问声好
Say hi to your new teammate, pop star Austin moon.
- 你好啊  - 你好
- Hey. - Hey.
你好  我叫艾尔
Hi. I'm Elle,
我还没男友呢
and single.
呃  很高兴认识你
Uh, nice to meet you.
你就是奥斯汀·穆恩啊
You're Austin moon.
真不敢相信我在和你说话
I can't believe you're talking to me.
你说什么
Huh?!
■
他比一只第一天在课上睡觉的裸羊还要害羞
哦
Oh.
好吧
Okay.
你好  我是
Hi. I'm...
只想让你知道  我可不是你的粉丝
Just so you know, I'm not a fan.
我讨厌流行音乐  讨厌爆米花
I hate pop music, and popcorn,
讨厌苏打水
and soda pop.
只要听起来差不多的我都讨厌
Anything with a pop in it.
也很高兴认识你
Nice to meet you too?
那是B.B. 她什么都讨厌
That's b.B. She hates everything.
那她怎么在合唱团里呢
Why is she in Glee club?
不加入合唱团是她所讨厌的
She hates not being in Glee club.
奥斯汀会对我们合唱团很有帮助
Austin's really gonna help our club.
他身高1米85
He's 6'1",
体重77公斤  能唱5个八度
170, has a five octave range,
仰卧推举的极限是80公斤
and he bench presses 175 pounds.
谢谢了  但这和合唱团有什么关系啊
Thanks, but what does that have to do with Glee club?
他还是个摔跤课教练
He's also the wrestling coach.
（注：夹头是摔跤比赛的常用手法）
他喜欢音乐  还喜欢夹头
He loves music and headlocks.
你太强壮了
You're so strong.
又太可爱了  我说过我是单身的了么
And cute. Did I mention I was single?
别烦人家了  艾尔
Back off, Elle.
奥斯汀
Austin,
欢迎加入合唱团
welcome to the team.
乐意参与  教练
Happy to be here, coach.
我很喜欢和我的朋友们同台演出
I love performing with my friends.
哼  和你的一部分朋友吧
Hmm. With some of your friends.
好的  现在把排练交给
Okay, I'm gonna turn over rehearsal
我们的队长负责
to our captain.
我们的口号是
What's our motto?
强音  响音  升音
Be strong, be loud, b-sharp!
没听见你的声音  迈尔斯
I didn't hear you, Miles.
强音  响音  升音
Be strong, be loud, b-sharp.
你这毛病以后再说吧
We'll work on that.
好了  各就各位  准备排练《心跳的旋律》
Okay, everybody. Line up for "heart beat. "
噢  奥斯汀
Oh, Austin.
给你看一下你要唱的部分
I'll show you your part.
哦  我早就知道了
Oh, I already know it.
德兹在午饭时就教会我所有的动作了
Dez taught me all the routines during lunch.
他大部分都学会了
He's got most of it down,
但我还是认为踢踏步
but I still think that a kick-step
相比转一圈还是要好多了
would work better than a twirl.
谢了  德兹  但我才是队长
Thanks, Dez, but I'm the captain
而你压根队员都不是
and you're not on the team.
你不拖好体育馆的地  难道要我来拖么
You wouldn't want me sweeping up the gym floor, would you?
也许吧
Kind of.
我可以感觉到
I can get your heart beat beat
你的心跳
beat beating like
我能感受到你心跳的韵律
I can get your heart beat beating like that
你知道你让我的心跳动不安
You know you got my heart beat beat beat beating like
噢-噢，噢 噢 噢
Oh-oh, oh oh oh
噢-噢 噢-噢
Oh-oh, oh-ohh.
好极了  各位
Bravo, people.
棒极了
Bravo.
真是美妙绝伦啊
That was perfect.
太好了  现在总算可以回家了
Great. Now we can go home.
没门  排练才刚开始呢
No way. Rehearsal's just starting.
奥斯汀
Austin,
你的声音很好  只不过下次要多笑笑
you sounded great. Just more smiling next time.
酷  而我觉得我们应该
Cool. And I was thinking we could
在动作上做一些改动
make a few changes to the routine
现在的这个有点过时了
since it's a little old-fashioned.
■
不是吧
过时了
Old-fashioned?
我才不会这么说  用“传统”会更好
I wouldn't call it that. Maybe "traditional,"
这才是裁判想看到的
but that's what judges look for.
这明显是用词不当啊
Okay, bad choice of words.
我的意思是  我们要把气氛带起来
What I meant was, we should rock things up.
不要像现在这么保守
Make it a little edgier.
啊  你的意思是说咱们要摇摇肩扭扭屁股
Oh, you want to add a little shaky-shaky-boom-boom?
算了  我可没这么说
Yeah, that's not what I meant.
没说的话就好了
I hope not.
我可不想再看一遍了
I never want to see that again.
这只是一个想法而已
It was just a thought.
思维要开放一点
Keep your mind open.
相信我吧
Trust me.
我知道我在做什么
I know what I'm doing.
我们绝对不可能输掉比赛的
There's no way we'll lose this competition.
不敢相信  我们居然输掉比赛了
I can't believe we lost that competition.
最重要的是我们参与了啊
But the important thing is that we participated.
只要参与了  我的学分就到手了
That's all I'm required to do to get my credit.
艾丽  麻烦在这儿签个名
Ally, can you initial this?
你们还拿了个奖杯  太棒了
And it's cool that you got a trophy
这能向你的妈妈证明  五年的歌咏课
that'll prove to your mom that five years of singing lessons
不算什么浪费钱
weren't a waste of money.
我要留着它
I'm keeping this.
别这么说  至少我们可以参加区域性比赛了
Hey, at least we qualified for regionals.
下次只要多加点
Next time, we just need to do dance moves
人们熟悉的舞步就好了
people have heard of.
（注：都是美国20世纪上半叶流行的舞步）
谁会没听说过查尔斯顿舞
Who hasn't heard of the Charleston
和林迪跳跃呢
and the lindy hop?
- 我  - 打出生起就没听说过
- Me. - Never in my life.
我们改做更新式的舞蹈动作  重新安排一下怎样
What if we did cooler dance moves to a new song arrangement?
我能感受到你心跳跳动的韵律
I can get your heart beat beat beat beating like
我能感受到你心跳就这样跳动
I can get your heart beat beating like that.
呜  我的心跳真是跳得那么快了
Whoo! My heart's beating like that.
我投票支持他的想法
I vote we do it his way.
好吧
Okay.
但是没有投票这一环节
There's no voting
因为我才是队长
because I am the captain.
而且这样就没有人声合唱的意义了
And that's not what a capella is about,
对吧  孙熙
right, sun hee?
■
为了得个好成绩  我无条件服从你  不管你错得多离谱
她觉得我是对的
She thinks I'm right.
艾丽  我知道这个对你来说多重要
Ally, I know how important this is to you.
所以我在提建议
That's why I'm making suggestions.
我想让你赢
I want you to win.
你确定不是因为
Are you sure it's not
你是个有名的流行歌手
because you're a famous pop star
就认为自己比合唱团队长还要厉害
and think you know better than the captain of the Glee club?
我没这么说  拜托
I didn't say that, but come on.
我还是知道不少的
I do know a few things.
我的舞台经验比你丰富很多
I've performed on a lot more stages than you.
亲们  别吵架好不好
Guys, let's not fight.
我们已经偏离中心问题了
We're losing focus of the real issue.
我应该加入合唱团
I should be on the team.
这你就别想了  德兹
Not gonna happen, Dez.
看  艾丽
Look, Ally,
我不想让你生气
I don't want to upset you,
但是我比较同意奥斯汀的
but I kind of agree with Austin
我不生气
I'm not upset.
不过就是我两个最好的朋友在我背后暗箭伤人
Why would I be upset that my two best friends
我有什么好生气的
are stabbing me in the back?
哦  那就好
Oh, phew.
我还以为你肯定不高兴的
I thought you were gonna be upset.
要是你和舞台大明星先生
If you and Mr. Superstar stage performer
知道那么多的话
know so much,
为什么不成立你们俩自己的合唱团
why don't you two start your own Glee club?
我们还真可以
Maybe we will.
谁加入我们
Who's with us?
我  我加入
Me! I'm with you.
不论健康或疾病  我愿意
In sickness and in health. I do.
好吧
Okay.
艾尔加入了我的队
Elle's joining my team.
还吓着我了
And scaring me.
你怎么选  迈尔斯
Who do you choose, Miles?
奥斯汀
Austin.
- 什么  - 奥斯汀
- What? - Austin.
哦  就直接跟他吧
Oh, just take him.
■
在选择之前  我要听听你们各自的优势和劣势
哦  真是的  她选你了
Oh, man. She picked you.
太好了
Yes.
那你呢  B.B
What about you, b. B.?
我讨厌你管事情的样子
I hate the way you run things,
我讨厌你的合唱团热病
I hate your Glee fever,
我甚至讨厌你的发型
I even hate your hair.
看起来她跟我了
So it looks like she's with me.
哦  不是  我还是跟着艾丽
Oh, no. I'm staying with Ally.
我更讨厌换队伍
I hate change even more.
哈
Ha.
你们确定要分开吗
You guys sure you want to break up?
你们一直都是搭档的
You've been partners forever,
而且一直都是朋友
and you've been friends forever.
我不想跟他们合作
I don't want to work with them.
我也不想跟她合作
And I don't want to work with her.
我也不愿意
Me neither.
你们知道只有一个合唱团
You do realize that only one Glee club
能代表学校参加区赛是吧
can represent our school at regionals?
那么  我猜我们都知道这意味着什么了
Well, I guess we know what that means.
是的
Yep.
让人声合唱之战打响吧
Let the a capella war begin.
或者说是
Or should I say,
让人声合唱之战打响吧
let the a capella war begin.
应该这么说
It should have gone,
让人声合唱之战打响吧  打响吧
let the a capella war begin begin
打响吧
begin!
从来没想过我两个最好的朋友
I never thought my two best friends
就这么抛弃我
would abandon me.
就是啊
I know.
现在你连比赛的人数都凑不齐了
Now you don't have enough members to compete.
到底要到哪去找男高音呢
Where oh where will you find a new tenor
时间太紧迫了
on such short notice?
要是你认识哪个人能
If only you knew someone who could
好了  德兹  你可以唱男高音
Fine, Dez. You can do it.
我
Me?!
哇哦  太惊喜了
Wow, this is a surprise.
好了  队员们  别管那帮自以为是的
Okay, b-sharps, forget those wannabes.
该排练了
Time to rehearse.
你最好赶紧排练  如果你们想打败
You'd better rehearse if you want to beat
（注：听起来也像“找麻烦”）
“找高音”队的话
"Looking for treble. "
很帅的名字  是吧
It's a cool name, huh?
才不是  太逊了
No. It's lame.
好吧  好吧  是挺酷的
Okay, fine, it's cool.
但我们还是会打败你们
But we're still gonna beat you.
希望你眼睛擦亮了
I hope you didn't eat too much lunch,
因为我们会要你好看
'cause you're about to get served.
哦  是吗
Oh yeah?
那告诉清洁大叔休息休息
Well, tell the janitor he can take some time off.
等我们把你打倒在地以后再收拾
'Cause we're gonna mop the floor with you.
好好在你那边呆着吧
Just stay on your side of the gym.
好了  队员们  我们来开嗓
All right, trebles, let's warm up.
我可以感受到心跳心跳的韵律
I can feel your heart beat beat beat beating like that.
看看那些菜鸟
Look at those rookies.
像小孩儿似的
They're like children.
我们来开嗓
Now let's do our warm-ups.
划  划  划小船
Row row row your boat
轻轻漂下岸
gently down the stream.
嗯
Mmm!
艾丽  找你的
Ally, it's for you.
是19世纪打来的
It's the 1800s.
他们找你要回他们的歌呢
They want their song back.
我刚刚收到一条未来的短信
Well, I just got a text from the future.
说你输了比赛
It says you lost the competition
因为你们队太逊了
'cause your whole team stinks.
大笑  皱眉头
Lol, frowny face!
我们不可能输的
There's no way we're gonna lose the competition.
奥斯汀知道怎么才能赢
Austin knows what it takes to win.
耶  我活在当下
Yeah, I live in the present
我代表现今
I'm all about today
我为历史歌唱
I sing about the past
民谣唱出永恒真理
when folks had something real to say
哦  现场音乐剧啊
Oh, snap! It's a musical throwdown.
哦错了  我是说
Oops. I mean,
哦  天啊
oh, snap
这是部现场的音乐剧
it's a musical throwdown.
让我坚持自我
Let me be me
这样内涵最多
'cause my way is cool
绝不羞愧
I'm not ashamed
守旧才值得举托
call me old school.
随你怎样说
Say what you want
王道就是我
my style will rule
保持鲜活
keeping it fresh
我们要创新开拓
call me new school.
守旧
Old school.
创新
New school.
守旧
Old school.
创新
New school.
守旧
Old school.
创新
New school.
这怎么回事
What's going on here?
嘿  你们俩要是想打架
Hey, if you two want to fight,
那边有摔跤毯
there's a wrestling mat in the corner.
我押十块  赌艾丽
I got 10 bucks on Ally.
不好意思哥们  她看起来攻击力比较强
Sorry, moon. She looks scrappy.
我没办法跟她合作  教练
I can't work with her, coach.
我也没办法跟她合作
And I can't work with him.
她一点都不友好  她觉得自己什么都知道
She's not nice. She thinks she knows
够了
Enough!
奥斯汀和艾丽
Austin and Ally,
你们俩都别来了
you're both out of Glee club.
你不能这样
You can't do this.
我的一切都贡献给合唱团了
Glee club is my life.
我的也是
Mine too.
你才进合唱团4天
You've been in Glee club four days.
把迈尔斯训练出声
Trying to get Miles to sing loudly
简直度日如年
feels like a lifetime.
他说得对
He's right.
你们俩在把事情搞得这么乱之前
Well, you both should have thought of that
就应该想到这些了
before you started this whole mess.
现在立刻出去
Now get out of here.
■
我要申请当队长
你们听到孙熙说的了  走
You heard Sun Hee. Get out.
对不起
I'm sorry, guys.
但是你知道我们必须得唱
But you know what we have to do.
这是个传统
It's tradition.
走  走  快走吧
Go, go, go away
我们将你们铭记在心
we'll miss you when you're gone
快乐的  欢快的  幸福的  美妙的
merrily, merrily, merrily, merrily
合唱团容不下二位
Glee club must go on.
停  停  停下来
Stop, stop, stop!
又怎么了
What's wrong now?
什么都不正常
Uh, everything.
我们得挑新服装
We need to find new costumes,
把韵律合一合
tighten our harmonies,
做相配的发型
get matching haircuts.
我讨厌他当新队长
I hate that he's the new captain.
我想奥斯汀了
I miss Austin.
这是我们有史以来分开最久的时候了
This is the longest we've ever been apart.
我现在都讨厌合唱团了
I hate Glee club now.
从来没听见过迈尔斯这么烦躁
I have never heard Miles so upset.
这都是你的错  德兹
This is all your fault, Dez.
谁让你当队长的
Who made you captain anyway?
手里有定调笛的
Well, he who holds the pitch pipe
就是掌权人
has the power.
■
我倒是真希望他把那个定调笛吞下去
谢谢你  孙熙
Thank you, sun hee.
你们怎么就不能像人家一样配合一点
Why can't you all be supportive like her?
再来一次
Let's try this again.
大家看我
Everyone watch me.
踢腿  迈步  踢腿  迈步
Kick-step, kick-step,
转圈  摆表情
spin, make a face.
甩头发  热锅蚂蚁  热锅蚂蚁
Flip your hair, hot sand, hot sand,
最后  超人造型
and superhero!
好了  翠西  你来一遍
All right, Trish. Now you try.
哼  不可能
Yeah, that's not gonna happen.
德兹  我有个想法
Dez, I have an idea.
艾丽  拜托
Ally, please,
我不会过去教你
I don't come over there and tell you
怎么扫地的
how to sweep the floor.
但是还是提醒一下  那边有个污点没擦到
But just so you know, you missed a spot.
你要保证“B大调队”能赢下区赛
Just promise me the b-sharps will win regionals.
我虽然不在合唱团了
I might not be in Glee club,
但这还是我生活中的一部分
but it's still a part of my life.
噢  真好
Aww. That's so sweet.
但现在我们不是“B大调”队了
But we're not the b-sharps anymore.
我们是“德兹小调”队
We're the Dez-tones.
不管叫什么名
Whatever your name is,
赢下比赛
just win.
你是我唯一的希望了
You're my only hope.
五  六  七  八
Five, six, seven, eight.
踢腿  迈步  踢腿  迈步
Kick-step, kick-step.
好吧
Okay.
唯一的希望也没了
There goes my hope.
艾丽  我们需要你回队
Ally, we need you back in Glee club.
我实在受不了德兹了
I can't take Dez anymore.
哦  看看谁又爬回来求助了
Oh, look who's come crawling back.
对不起还不行吗
I'm sorry.
我只不过想赢而已
I just wanted to win.
但是唯一的办法
But the only way that's gonna happen
就是你和奥斯汀讲和
is if you and Austin make up.
就算我想回去
Even if I wanted to come back,
那西蒙教练那怎么办
what about coach Simmons?
他说不好让我们摔跤才能归队
He'll probably make us wrestle to get back on the team.
我知道我看起来很强
I know I look tough,
但是我不想让人发现我是个菜包
but I don't want people to find out that I'm not.
这是我们俩的秘密
That'll be our little secret.
教练的事交给我
Leave the coach to me.
那你会回来吗
So will you come back?
我不知道我还能不能感染上合唱团热病了
I don't know if I can catch Glee fever again.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
它可是传染的哟
It's contagious.
没用的
That's not gonna work.
哦
Ohh.
说不好哦
I don't know.
我感觉它已经传播出去了
I think it's spreading.
等等  我确实感觉到了
Wait. I do feel something.
啊哈
Uh-huh.
我的手指开始疼了
My fingers are starting to tingle.
- 哦  是啊  - 我的手变成爵士手了
- Oh, yeah. - My hands are getting jazzy.
- 哦  不  - 翠西  叫医生来
- Oh, no. - Trish, call the doctor.
别告诉我你得了
Don't tell me you have
合唱团热病
Glee fever.
真情永不褪
Never gonna fade
我们永恒不改
we are timeless
we are timeless.
很好听
That sounds good.
因为是我们一起写的
That's 'cause we wrote it together.
是啊  我们一起的时候什么都会变得更好
Yeah. Everything's better when we work together.
是啊
I know.
对不起我分开了合唱团
I'm sorry I split up the club.
但是你当队长的时候
But when you were captain
怎么说比较委婉呢
How can I put this nicely?
你是个烦人的控制怪
You were an annoying control freak.
这叫委婉
That's nicely?
对不起  但这是事实
Sorry. But it's true.
还是对不起
Sorry again.
这怎么叫控制欲强呢
What's so controlling
我就是希望一切都按照我的想法来
about wanting everything my way
不想采用别人的建议而已
and not listening to anyone else's ideas?
好吧
Okay.
说出来的时候
When I say it out loud,
确实不怎么好
it does sound pretty bad.
听着  不都是你的错
Look, it wasn't all your fault.
我应该知道我越权了
I should have known I was stepping on your toes.
但我只是想帮忙
But I was just trying to help.
我知道
I know.
你知道为什么我对合唱团这么狂热么
You know why I'm so crazy about Glee club?
这是唯一一件我可以亲自着手做所有事的
It's the one thing where I get to do everything.
音乐  编舞
The music, the choreography,
都是我的
it's all mine.
我明白
I get it.
我准备演唱会的时候也是这样的
That's what I get to do with my concerts.
只不过我不是个控制狂
Only I'm not an annoying control freak.
你乐队可不是这么说的啊
That's not what your band says.
那你觉得我们和好
So what do you say we get back together
一起赢下区赛怎么样
and go win regionals?
按照你的想法来
We'll do it your way.
不
No.
按照我们的想法来
We'll do it our way.
我还以为合唱团必须都是你的啊
But I thought Glee club had to be all yours.
不管那个  赢下比赛就好
Forget that. I want to win.
我也是  开动吧
Yeah, me too. Let's do this.
教练  这周末就是区赛了
Coach, regionals are this weekend.
我们需要新服装  无线麦
We need new costumes, wireless mics,
还有很多的身体亮粉
way more body glitter.
孩子  我再给你身体亮粉
Son, if I gave you any more body glitter,
你就要变成迪斯科灯球了
you'd look like a disco ball.
啊  提醒我了  我们需要一个迪斯科灯球
Ah, that reminds me. We need a disco ball.
教练  我想跟你谈谈让奥斯汀和艾丽
Coach, I wanted to talk to you about letting Austin and Ally
归队的事  我保证
back into Glee club. I promise
行听你的
They're in.
别让这个小笨蛋靠近我就好
Just keep this fool away from me.
好的  教练
You got it, coach.
啊  真高兴我们的队伍又齐了
Ah, I'm glad the team's back together.
有奥斯汀和艾丽的才华  再加上我的领导力
With Austin and Ally's talent and my leadership,
我们区赛肯定能得第一
we're gonna win regionals.
艾丽是队长
Ally's captain again.
呃  但是我手上有定调笛啊
Uh, but I have the pitch pipe.
现在你没有了
And now you don't.
前进的路上怎能没有你
There's no way I could make it without ya
你不可或缺  你无可替代
do it without ya, be here without ya
快乐需要与你分享
it's no no fun when you're doing it solo
在你身边总有惊喜
with you it's like "Whoa"
而且我还知道
yeah, and I know
我为梦想而奋斗
I own this dream
因为有你伴我左右
'cause I got you with me
是否  是否能感觉得到  是否  是否  能感觉得到
can you, can you feel, can you, can you, can you feel
- 是否能  - 感觉得到
- can you feel it - can you feel it
开足  开足  开足音量
turn it up, up, up
是否能感觉得到
Can you feel it
开足  开足  开足音量
turn it up, up, up
- 是否能  - 感觉得到
- can you feel it - can you feel it
- 开足  开足  开足音量  - 是否感受得到
- turn it up, up, up - feel it, feel it, it feel
是否感受  感受得到
can you feel it, feel it, feel it
感受得到  喔-哦-哦  哦-哦
feel it, whoa-oh-oh, oh-ohh
我的成功在望
that's what I'm gonna get
喔-哦-哦  哦-哦
whoa-oh-oh, oh-ohh
我的成功在望
that's what I'm gonna get
因为我知道我会成功
yeah, 'cause I know that I'll make it
我要挤爆网络
overload the Internet
得到百万点击量
a billion hits is what I'll get
站上舞台
step right up on the stage
释放真我
free yourself from the cage
抽张卡片  猜猜看
pick a card and guess it, girl
告诉你  姑娘
here's a lesson, girl
这只是一个幻象
it's just an illusion
摇滚出自我之道
I've got that rock and roll
耶  耶
yeah, yeah
我会让你失控尖叫
I'll make you lose control
耶  耶
yeah, yeah
一起来我的地盘共舞
come on and dance to my flow
耶  耶
yeah, yeah
因为摇滚出自
'cause I got what I got
你是否知道
don't you know
摇滚出自我之道
I got that rock and roll
噢-噢  噢-噢
oh-oh, oh-oh
噢-噢-噢-噢
oh-oh-oh-oh
呐 呐 呐 呐 呐
na na na na na
电台放着我的歌
heard it on the radio
呐 呐 呐
na na na
回放  回放一遍
play it back, play it back one time
哦 哦 哦
oh oh oh
这就是我
I'm finally me
万事俱备
I got everything I need
真实展现  我的一切
what you get is what you see
此刻
I-I
享受自我
I'm finally me
从未如此  无拘无束
and I never felt so free
不再刻上
there's no one else
旁人烙印
I'm trying to be
此刻  回归自我
I'm finally me
嘿-嘿  嘿-嘿  喔
hey-hey, hey-hey, Whoo
我最爱的事
I love the things you do
就是你能做你想做的事
it's how you do the things you love
但这不是一首情歌
but it's not a love song
- 嘿-嘿  嘿-嘿  - 但这不是情歌
- hey-hey, hey-hey - it's not a love song
噢-噢-噢噢
oh-oh-ohh
任你称我滔天罪犯
call me criminal
不可否认 你牵动我的每根神经
I won't deny you make me want it all
想念你的一切
everything you are
来锁上我的心
so lock it up
不必迟疑不决
go on and try it
无论你的 一颦一蹙 一举一动 我誓要偷走你的心
no matter what you do, I'm gonna steal your heart
永不低头
don't look down down
down down
永不低头
Down down down
因为
'cause
前进的路上怎能没有你
there's no way I could make it without ya
你不可或缺  你无可替代
do it without ya, be here without ya
快乐需要与你分享
it's no fun when you're doing it solo
在你身边总有惊喜
with you it's like "Whoa"
而且我还知道
yeah, and I know
- 嘿 嘿 嘿  - 噢
- hey hey hey - ohh
- 嘿 嘿  - 你不可或缺
- hey hey - be here without you
你无可替代
be here without you
无可  替代
out you, out you
耶
yeah!
总算拿到你的奖杯了
You got your trophy.
你成功了
You did it.
是我们成功了
We did it.
这个属于我们所有人
This belongs to all of us.
你应该留着
You should keep it.
这对你来说太重要了
It means the most to you.
是啊  我们不在乎奖杯的
Yeah, we don't care about the trophy.
让我们做合唱团的一员就够了
Just getting to be on the team was its own reward.
这样吧
Tell you what
我把它摆在柜台上
I'll keep this on the counter
这样我们就都能看到了
so we can all enjoy it.
- 好啊  - 就这么定了
- Great.  - Awesome.
- 回见了  - 再见
- See you later.  - Bye.
- 那是我的  - 明明是我的
- I want it!  - It's mine!
- 你们自己留着吧  - 我反正不要了
- You guys can have it.  - I don't want it.